like so I just was like what's about to
happen so like it was like the Seas
parted the nice dude then this other
dude this other dude and this one little
short ball-headed come up to me
and he's like you need to get the out of
here he's yeah like the F Fu like it's
spit
spit I said what are you talking about
what why do I need to get out of here
cuz we said you need to get out of
here these are the moments when you
really are like why don't I know
Taekwondo you know cuz you like I could
get arrested but I would have given
them oh my God are you okay
sorry but see I would have given them
that you see you see I could have given
them all of
[Music]
that